Guide to the Stanford University, Plant Services Office, Records
Stanford University. Libraries.
- Stanford University Building Plans (negative prints), Accession ARCH-1991-123
  - President's Residence - Front Elevation (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - President's Residence - Rear Elevation (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - President's Residence - Side Elevation (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - President's Residence - Side Elevation (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - President's Residence - Arch in Main Hall (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - President's Residence - Foundation Plan (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - President's Residence - First floor Plan (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - President's Residence - Second floor Plan (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - President's Residence - Roof & Attic Plan (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Proposed House (Wolfe & McKenzie Arch.} - Front Elevation (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Proposed House - Side Elevation (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Proposed House - Side Elevation (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Proposed. House - Foundation, Sewer, and Heating Plan (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Proposed. House - First floor Plan (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Proposed House - Second floor Plan (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Proposed. House - Roof & Attic Plan (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Proposed House - Dining Rm. Sideboard; Reception Hall showing stairs; Parlor Seat & Mantle; Reception Hall Fireplace (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Delta Upsilon House (A.B. Clark) - Front Elevation (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Delta Upsilon House - Elevation R (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Delta Upsilon House - Elevation L (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Delta Upsilon House - Foundation Plan (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Delta Upsilon House - First Floor Plan (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Delta Upsilon House - Second Floor Plan (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Delta Upsilon House - Third Floor & Roof Plan (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Delta Upsilon House - Elevations in hall; elev. of dining rm. toward sideboard; Section through Dining nn. (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Delta Upsilon House - Elevation in Chaper hall (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Delta Upsilon House - Details of Construction (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Club House (Charles D. Austin - 1891) - Front Elevation (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Club House - Side Elevation (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Club House - Foundation Plan (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Club House - First floor Plan (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Club House - Second floor Plan (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - Club House - Roof Plan (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - Club House - Front Elevation (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - Proposed House (A.W. Smith) Front Elevation (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - Proposed House - Rear Elevation (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - Proposed House - South Elevation (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - Proposed House - North Elevation (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - Proposed House - Basement Plan (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - Proposed House - First floor Plan (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - Proposed House - Second Floor Plan (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - Proposed House - Attic Plan (Box 1, Folder 62)
  - Proposed House - Out Building Plans and Elevations (Box 1, Folder 63)
  - Two Story Frame Cottage (C.E. Hodges - Owner Prof. Ryan) - Fireplace (Box 1, Folder 64)
  - Two Story Frame Cottage - ELevation, Plan, Section (Box 1, Folder 65)
  - Two Story Frame Cottage - Details (Box 1, Folder 66)
  - Two Story Frame Cottage - Full Size Details of Window Casings (Box 1, Folder 67)
  - Two Story Frame Cottage - Tool & Automobile House (Box 1, Folder 68)
  - Phi Delta Theta Fraternity House 5-5207 (Henry A. Schulze) Front Elev. (Box 1, Folder 69)
  - Phi Delta Theta Fraternity House - Rear Elevation (Box 1, Folder 70)
  - Phi Delta Theta Fraternity House - North Elevation (Box 1, Folder 71)
  - Phi Delta Theta Fraternity House - Plan of Foundation (Box 1, Folder 72)
  - Phi Delta Theta Fraternity House - First Floor Plan (Box 1, Folder 73)
  - Phi Delta Theta Fraternity House - South Elevation (Box 1, Folder 74)
  - Phi Delta Theta Fraternity House - Second Floor Plan (Box 1, Folder 75)
  - Phi Delta Theta Fraternity House - Third Floor Plan (Box 1, Folder 76)
  - Phi Delta Theta Fraternity House - Sees. of 1st Fl.; details of window / door (Box 1, Folder 77)
  - Club House - Front Elevation (Box 1, Folder 78)
  - Club House - Side Elevation (Box 1, Folder 79)
  - Club House - Foundation Plan (Box 1, Folder 80)
  - Club House - First Floor Plan (Box 1, Folder 81)
  - Club House - Second Floor Plan (Box 1, Folder 82)
  - Club House - Roof Plan (Box 1, Folder 83)
  - Cottage No. 7 (Shepley Rutan & Coolidge) - First & Second Floor Plans (Box 1, Folder 84)
  - Cottage No. 7 - Front & Side Elevations (Box 1, Folder 85)
  - Cottage No.3 - Side & Front Elevations (Box 1, Folder 86)
  - Cottages No.5 & 6 - Foundation Plan (Box 1, Folder 87)
  - Cottages No.3 & 4 - First & Second Floor Plans (Box 1, Folder 88)
  - Semi-Detached House #13 (Shepley Rutan Coolidge) -1st & 2nd Plans (Box 1, Folder 89)
  - Semi-Detached House #13 - Front and Side Elevations (Box 1, Folder 90)
  - Semi-Detached House #13 - Foundation Plan (Box 1, Folder 91)
  - Semi-Detached House #13 - Second Floor & Roof Plans (Box 1, Folder 92)
  - Semi-Detached House #13 - Attic and Roof Plan (Box 1, Folder 93)
  - Double Cottage No. 14 (Charles Austin) - Attic and Foundation Plans (Box 1, Folder 94)
  - Double Cottage No. 14 - First and Second Floor Plans (Box 1, Folder 95)
  - Double Cottage No. 14 - Front and Side Elevations (Box 1, Folder 96)
  - Residence No. 12 - Front and Side Elevations (Box 1, Folder 97)
  - Residence No. 12 - Foundation and Roof Plans (Box 1, Folder 98)
  - Residence No. 12 - First and Second Floor Plans (Box 1, Folder 99)
  - Owens House (02-917) - Front Elevation (Box 1, Folder 100)
  - Cottages 18 & 19 - Side and Rear Elevations (Box 1, Folder 101)
  - Cottages 18 & 19 - Side and Rear Elevations (Box 1, Folder 102)
  - Cottages 18 & 19 - Roof & Attic and Foundation Plans (Box 1, Folder 103)
  - Cottages 18 & 19 - First and Second Floor Plans (Box 1, Folder 104)
  - Durand-Kirkman House - North and West Elevations (Box 1, Folder 105)
  - Durand-Kirkman House - South and East Elevations (Box 1, Folder 106)
  - Durand-Kirkman House - Attic-Roof & Foundation Plans (Box 1, Folder 107)
  - Durand-Kirkman House - First and Second Floor Plans (Box 1, Folder 108)
  - Proposed House (Charles E. Hodges) - Front Elevation (Box 1, Folder 109)
  - Proposed House - Rear Elevation (Box 1, Folder 110)
  - Proposed House - First Floor Plan (Box 1, Folder 111)
  - Proposed House - Side Elevation (Box 1, Folder 112)
  - Proposed Residence (for Herbert E. Coil - C. E. Hodges) - 2nd Floor Plan (Box 1, Folder 113)
  - Proposed House (C.E. Hodges) - Side Elevation (Box 1, Folder 114)
  - Proposed House - Foundation Plan (Box 1, Folder 115)
  - Sigma Alpha Epsilon Fraternity House - 534 Salvatierra (Tharp and Holmes)--Front Elevation (Box 1, Folder 116)
  - Sigma Alpha Epsilon Fraternity House· Rear Elevation (Box 1, Folder 117)
  - Sigma Alpha Epsilon Fraternity House - Side Elevation (Box 1, Folder 118)
  - Sigma Alpha Epsilon Fraternity House· Transverse Section (Box 1, Folder 119)
  - Sigma Alpha Epsilon Fraternity House - Longitudinal Section (Box 1, Folder 120)
  - Sigma Alpha Epsilon Fraternity House· Foundation & Basement Plan (Box 1, Folder 121)
  - Sigma Alpha Epsilon Fraternity House - Second Floor Plan (Box 1, Folder 122)
  - Proposed Residence (C.E. Hodges) - Front Elevation (Box 1, Folder 123)
  - Proposed Stable (C.E. Hodges) - Front Elevation (Box 1, Folder 124)
  - Proposed Residence - Front Elevation (Box 1, Folder 125)
  - Proposed Residence - Rear Elevation (Box 1, Folder 126)
  - Proposed Residence - Side Elevation (Box 1, Folder 127)
  - Proposed Residence - Basement Plan (Box 1, Folder 128)
  - Proposed Residence - First Floor Plan (Box 1, Folder 129)
  - Proposed Residence - Second Floor Plan (Box 1, Folder 130)
  - Proposed Residence (A.W. Smith) - Rear & Side Elevations (Box 1, Folder 131)
  - Proposed Residence - Basement and Attic Plan (Box 1, Folder 132)
  - Proposed Residence - First and Second Floor Plans (Box 1, Folder 133)
  - Residence No. 13 (Shepley Rutan & Coolidge) - Front & Side Elevation (Box 1, Folder 134)
  - Residence No. 13 - Foundation & Roof Plans (Box 1, Folder 135)
  - Residence No. 13 - First & Second Floor Plans (Box 1, Folder 136)
  - Residence (for Prof. A.W. Smith by C.E. Hodges)-- Front & Side Elev. (Box 1, Folder 137)
  - Residence for A.W. Smith - Foundation & Roof Plans (Box 1, Folder 138)
  - Residence for A.W. Smith - First and Second Floor Plans (Box 1, Folder 139)
  - Cottages nos. 24-27 - 1st & 2nd Floor Plans, Front Elevation (Box 1, Folder 140)
  - Cottages nos. 24-27 - Foundation Plan & Side Elevation (Box 1, Folder 141)
  - Cottages nos. 24-27 - Foundation & Roof Plans (Box 1, Folder 142)
  - Fraternity? - Second Floor Plan (Box 1, Folder 143)
  - Fraternity? - Side Elevation (Box 1, Folder 144)
  - Fraternity? - First Floor Plan (Box 1, Folder 145)
  - Cottage - C.E. Hodges - Front and Side Elevations (Box 1, Folder 146)
  - Cottage - Foundation and Roof/Attic Plan (Box 1, Folder 147)
  - Proposed Alterations and Additions to Two story Brick Bldg. - C.E. Hodges - First and Second Floor Plans (Box 1, Folder 148)
  - School House & Residence (to be erected at University Park, P.A.) C.E. Hodges - First Floor Plan (Box 1, Folder 149)
  - School House & Residence - Second Floor Plan (Box 1, Folder 150)
  - Plot Plans - Houses A & B - Diagram of Escavations (Box 1, Folder 151)
  - Plot Plans - Lane B (Box 1, Folder 152)
  - Additions to residence of Charles G. Lathrop - Front Elevation (Box 1, Folder 153)
  - Additions to residence of Charles G. Lathrop - Rear Elevation (Box 1, Folder 154)
  - Additions to residence of Charles G. Lathrop - Side Elevation (Box 1, Folder 155)
  - Additions to residence of Charles G. Lathrop - Basement Plan (Box 1, Folder 156)
  - Additions to residence of Charles G. Lathrop - First Floor Plan (Box 1, Folder 157)
  - Additions to residence of Charles G. Lathrop - Second Floor Plan (Box 1, Folder 158)
  - Additions to residence of Charles G. Lathrop - Attic Plan (Box 1, Folder 159)
  - Additions to residence of Charles G. Lathrop - Details of Dining Rm. (Box 1, Folder 160)
  - Additions to residence of Charles G. Lathrop - South Elev. of Dining Room; Section & Plan of China Clos. (Box 1, Folder 161)
  - Proposed Residence - (C.G. Lathrop owner, C.E. Hodges) - First Floor Plan (Box 1, Folder 162)
  - Proposed Residence - Roof Plan (Box 1, Folder 163)
  - Addition used for Bathrooms - Front, Side Elev. - 1st & 2nd Floors (Box 1, Folder 164)
  - Stable for C.G. Lathrop - First Floor Plan; Front Elevation (Box 1, Folder 165)
  - Proposed Alters. and Adds. to stable at Alta Vista (Lathrop) 1st Fl. Plan (Box 1, Folder 166)
  - Stable - Second Floor Plan; Longitudinal Section (Box 1, Folder 167)
  - Proposed Alters. and Adds. to stable at Alta Vista (Lathrop) 2nd Fl. Plan (Box 1, Folder 168)
  - Proposed Alters. and Adds. to stable at Alta Vista (Lathrop) 2nd Fl. Plan (Box 1, Folder 169)
  - Alta Vista Stables - First Floor Plan (Box 1, Folder 170)
  - Alta Vista Stables - First Floor Plan (Box 1, Folder 171)
  - Alta Vista Stables - Second Floor Front Plan (Box 1, Folder 172)
  - Windmill Tower for C.G. Lathrop - Elevation, Foundation Plan (Box 1, Folder 173)
  - Inside Finish - lathrop'S House (Box 1, Folder 174)
  - Alta Vista Stables - Front and Rear Elevation, First Floor Plan (Box 1, Folder 175)
  - Alta Vista Stables - Front Elevation, Section (Box 1, Folder 176)
  - Cooksey House (Phi Kappa Psi 11-270) - First Floor Plan (Box 1, Folder 177)
  - Cooksey House - Second Floor Plan (Box 1, Folder 178)
  - Cooksey ~ouse - Third Floor Plan (Box 1, Folder 179)
  - Cooksey House - North East Elevation (Box 1, Folder 180)
  - Cooksey House - Rear Elevation (Box 1, Folder 181)
  - Cooksey House - North Elevation (Box 1, Folder 182)
  - Cooksey House - South Elevation (Box 1, Folder 183)
  - Cooksey House - Foundation Plan (Box 1, Folder 184)
  - Cooksey House - Roof Pian (Box 1, Folder 185)
  - Residence for Prof. G.M. Richardson (Curtis Tobey Jr.) - Front Elev. (Box 1, Folder 186)
  - Residence for Prof. G.M. Richardson - Side Elevation (Box 1, Folder 187)
  - Residence for Prof. G.M. Richardson - Foundation Plan (Box 1, Folder 188)
  - Residence for Prof. G.M. Richardson - First Floor Plan (Box 1, Folder 189)
  - Residence for Prof. G.M. Richardson - Second Floor Plan (Box 1, Folder 190)
  - Proposed Residence (C.E. Hodges) - Front & Side Elevations (Box 1, Folder 191)
  - Proposed Residence - First & Second Floor Plans (Box 1, Folder 192)
  - Residence #20 - Section of Kitchen and Dining Room (Box 1, Folder 193)
  - Section (Box 1, Folder 194)
  - Geology Comer (01-320) - Foundation Plan (Box 1, Folder 195)
  - Geology Comer - First Floor Plan (Box 1, Folder 196)
  - Geology Comer - Second Floor Plan (Box 1, Folder 197)
  - Geology Comer - Attic Plan (Box 1, Folder 198)
  - Geology Comer - West Elev. & Section on line AB (Box 1, Folder 199)
  - Geology Comer - South Elev. & Section on line EF (Box 1, Folder 200)
  - Geology Comer - Section on line CD & Side Elevation (Box 1, Folder 201)
  - Geology Comer - Foundation Plan (Box 1, Folder 202)
  - Geology Comer - First Floor Plan (Box 1, Folder 203)
  - Geology Comer - Second Floor Plan (Box 1, Folder 204)
  - Geology Comer - Attic Plan (Box 1, Folder 205)
  - Phi Sig House (11-190) - Remodeling: 2nd Roor Plans (old and new) (Box 1, Folder 206)
  - Phi Sig House - North and South Elevations (old and new) (Box 1, Folder 207)
  - Phi Sig House - East and West Elevations (old and new) (Box 1, Folder 208)
  - Phi Sig House - Cross and Longitudinal Sections (old and new) (Box 1, Folder 209)
  - Phi Sig House - Details: stairs, front entrance; Views (Box 1, Folder 210)
  - Phi Sig House - First Floor Plan (old and new) (Box 1, Folder 211)
  - Phi Sig House - Cross Section & Basement Plan (new) (Box 1, Folder 212)
  - Proposed House - Rear Elevation (Box 1, Folder 213)
  - Proposed House - Longitudinal Section (Box 1, Folder 214)
  - Proposed House - Plan View (Box 1, Folder 215)
  - Proposed House - Second Floor Plan (Box 1, Folder 216)
  - Bunk House - Gridley Ranch - Details (Box 1, Folder 217)
  - Bunk House - First Floor Plan; Section; Front Elevation (Box 1, Folder 218)
  - Servant's House -- Gridley Ranch - Plan, Section, Elevation (Box 1, Folder 219)
  - Servant's House - Gridley Ranch - Details (Box 1, Folder 220)
  - Bunk House - Foundation Plan (Box 1, Folder 221)
  - Mess House - Gridley Ranch - Roor and Roof Plan (Box 1, Folder 222)
  - Mess House - Foundation & Floor plans; Elev. & Sections (Box 1, Folder 223)
  - Superintendent's House - South Side Elev. (Box 1, Folder 224)
  - Superintendent's House - Foundation Plan (Box 1, Folder 225)
  - Superintendent's House - Details of Dining Room (Box 1, Folder 226)
  - Superintendent's House - Fire Place; end of Living Room (Box 1, Folder 227)
  - Superintendent's House - Floor Plan (Box 1, Folder 228)
  - Superintendent's House - North Side Elevation (Box 1, Folder 229)
  - Superintendent's House - Front and Rear Elevation (Box 1, Folder 230)
  - Office Building - Gridley Ranch - Floor Plan (Box 1, Folder 231)
  - Office Building - Gridley Ranch - Section and Side Elevation (Box 1, Folder 232)
  - Office Building - Gridley Ranch -- Rear Elevation (Box 1, Folder 233)
  - Office Building - Gridley Ranch - Front Elevation (Box 1, Folder 234)
  - Drain Plan south of Memorial Church (Box 2, Folder DI-2)
  - Plan of Pavement in Quad and Arcades (SW & NW Quarter) (Box 2, Folder DI-3)
  - Plan of Pavement in Quad and Arcades (SE & NE Quarter) (Box 2, Folder DI-4)
  - Large Dormitory No.1 - Basement Plan (Shepley Rutan & Coolidge) (Box 2, Folder D2-3)
  - Large Dormitory No. 1 - Basement Plan (Box 2, Folder D2-3b)
  - Large DOrmitory No. 1 - Basement Plan (Box 2, Folder D2-3b)
  - Profile Sewer (Quadrangle) (Box 2, Folder D2-9b)
  - Profile Sewer (Quadrangle) (Box 2, Folder D2-9b)
  - Profiles of Outlet along Embarcadero Road (Box 2, Folder D2-16)
  - Profiles of Outlet along Embarcadero Road - Section II (Box 2, Folder D2-16)
  - Sewer System Engineering Labs (Box 2, Folder D2-24)
  - Palm Drive and Oval (drainage) (Box 2, Folder E3-2)
  - Map showing Proposed location of new athletic field - 1904 (Box 2, Folder E3-8)
  - Map showing Proposed location of new athletic field -1904 (Box 2, Folder E3-8)
  - Profile of University A venue (North and South center line) (Box 2, Folder E3-12)
  - Preliminary profiles: streets east and west of quad.; through center of tomb, circle, and main quad (Box 2, Folder E3-17)
  - Grading Plans for grounds about tomb (Box 2, Folder E3-18)
  - Grading Plans for grounds about tomb (Box 2, Folder E3-18b)
  - Grading Plans fo, grounds about tomb (Box 2, Folder E3-18b)
  - Plat of Cooksey Place (Nov. 23-281906) (Box 2, Folder E3-22)
  - Proposed Location of the Stanford Bookstore Building (Box 2, Folder E3-23)
  - Plan of Existing and Proposed Shops (Box 2, Folder E3-24)
  - Map showing location of shops completed & under construction 5/08 (Box 2, Folder E3-24b)
  - Peninsular Railroad Co. Standard Roadbed (Box 2, Folder E3-25)
  - Plot showing Toe of Slope on location through Stanford (Box 2, Folder E3-26)
  - Plot showing Toe of Slope on location through Stanford (Box 2, Folder E3-26)
  - Plot showing Toe of Slope on location through Stanford (Box 2, Folder E3-26)
  - Map showing proposed extension of Alma St. through the S. Pacific RR company's right of way & Stanford Estate to S.F. & San Jose Rd. (Box 2, Folder E3-27)
  - Estimate of cast of proposed under grade R.R. Crossing of Palo Alto Ave. across S. Pacific R.R. tracks (Box 2, Folder E3-28)
  - Index to profiles (Box 2, Folder E3-31)
  - Map of four lots along Lasuen Ave. (Box 2, Folder E3-33)
  - Grading; elevation; map showing proposed street (Box 2, Folder E3-35)
  - Plat of Lasuen Street from Quad. to County Road (Box 2, Folder E3-41)
  - Profiles (Box 2, Folder E3 ....)
  - Profiles (Box 2, Folder E3 ....)
  - Girl's Gymnasium - Front Elevation (Shepley Rutan Architect> (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Girl's Gymnasium - Side Elevation (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Girl's GymnaSium - Foundation Plan (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Girl's Gymnasium - Gallery Plan (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Roble Gymnasium Addition - (04-650) Side Elevation (A.J. Bain Architect) (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Roble Gymnasium Addition - Section and Foudation Plan (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Roble Gymnasium Addition - Floor Plan (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Roble Gymnasium Addition - Front Elevation (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Roble Gymnasium Addition - ''Building at Present" (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Proposed Boys Gym - Front Elevation (Shepley Rutan Architect) (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Proposed Boys Gym - Side Elevation (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Proposed Boys Gym - Steam Heating and Plumbing; Shower/Bath (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Post Office - (02-01) Side Elevation (Chad. Ed. Hodges. Resident Architect> (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Post Office - Foundation Plan (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Post Office - First Floor Plan (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Post Office - Detail of Truss (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Post Office - Roof Plan (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Post Office - Detail of Outside Doors (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - University Bookstore - (03-50) North and Front Elevation (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - University Bookstore - South and Rear Elevation (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - University Bookstore - Foundation Plan (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - University Bookstore - Main Floor Plan (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Leland Stanford Jr. Museum - (07-100) Percy & Hamilton Architects (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Stanford Museum - Transverse Sec. & One Halt Sec. through Rotunda One half plan of Dome (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Stanford Museum - Scale Detail of Skylight of Central Rotunda (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Stanford Museum - Half Elevation and Sec. of Rotunda (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Additions to Museum - Elevation & Sec. of Rotunda Piers Elevation of Center Wall of Rotunda (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Additions to Museum - Detail Plan of Rotunda Foundations (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Additions to Museum - First Floor Plan (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Additions to Museum - Plan of Gallery Floor showing Girders (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Additions to Museum - Rotunda Roof (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Additions to Museum - Plan of Dome (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Additions to Museum - Plan of Dome & Ceiling (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Additions to Museum - Plan of C.I. Base and Pillar (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Additions to Museum - Detail of Dome (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Additions to Museum - Detail of Truss (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Additions to Museum - Detail of Dome (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Museum Bldg. Remodeling N.W. cor. rooms for Med. Labs & Qassrooms - Anatomy (07-50) Roof Plan (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - Museum Bldg. Remodeling - 2nd Floor Plan; Section; Detail of Gutter; Detail of Doors; Detail of Windows (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - Museum Bldg. Remodeling - Front Elevation; Section AB; Details of Doors, Arch. Gutter (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - Museum Bldg. Remodeling - East & West Elevation of D.E.D.; Roof Plan (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - Museum Bldg. Remodeling - Side Elevation; Sec. AB; Front Elev.; Detail of Doors (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - Museum Bldg. Remodeling - Basement & 1st Floor Plans (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - Museum Bldg. Remodeling - Detail of Arch, Case; Roof Plan (Box 3, Folder 47)
  - Museum Bldg. Remodeling - Basement & 1st Floor Plans; East Elev. (Box 3, Folder 48)
  - Museum Bldg. Remodeling - Basement & 1st Floor Plans (Box 3, Folder 49)
  - Museum Bldg. Remodeling - Basement & 1st Floor Plans (Box 3, Folder 50)
  - Museum Bldg. Remodeling - Side Elevation (Box 3, Folder 51)
  - Museuril Bldg. Remodeling -1st and 2nd Floor Plans (Box 3, Folder 52)
  - Museum Bldg. Remodeling - Detail of Window to swing (Box 3, Folder 53)
  - Additions to Museum - Detail Plan of Rotunda (Box 3, Folder 54)
  - Old Chemistry Building - (07-200) Clinton Day Architect - Front Elev. (Box 3, Folder 55)
  - Old ChemiStry Building - Rear Elevation (Box 3, Folder 56)
  - Old Chemistry Building - Side Elevation (Box 3, Folder 57)
  - Old Chemistry Building - Front and Rear Elev. of Assay Lab. (Box 3, Folder 58)
  - Old Chemistry Building - Cross Section (Box 3, Folder 59)
  - Old Chemistry Building - Longitudinal Section (Box 3, Folder 60)
  - Old Chemistry Building - Foundation Plan (Box 3, Folder 61)
  - Old Chemistry Building - Basement Floor Plan (Box 3, Folder 62)
  - Old Chemistry Building - Basement Floor Plan (Box 3, Folder 63)
  - Old Chemistry Building - First Floor Plan (Box 3, Folder 64)
  - Old Chemistry Building - First Floor Plan (Box 3, Folder 65)
  - Old Chemistry Building - Second Floor Plan (Box 3, Folder 66)
  - Old Chemistry Building - Second Floor Plan (Box 3, Folder 67)
  - Old Chemistry Building - Second Floor Plan (Box 3, Folder 68)
  - Old ChemiStry Building - Second Floor Plan (Box 3, Folder 69)
  - Old Chemistry Building - Attic and Roof Plan (Box 3, Folder 70)
  - Old Chemistry Building - Attic and Roof Plan (Box 3, Folder 71)
  - Old Chemistry Building - Attic and Roof Plan (Box 3, Folder 72)
  - Old Chemistry Building - ''Typical Section on line AA" (Box 3, Folder 73)
  - Old Chemistry Building - Ventilation of Bldg. (Box 3, Folder 74)
  - Old Chemistry Building - Heaters for Chemistry Laboratories (Box 3, Folder 75)
  - Old Chemistry Building - Ventilators for Qualitative Lab. (Box 3, Folder 76)
  - Old Chemistry Building - Arrangement of Ventilating System (Box 3, Folder 77)
  - Old Chemistry Building - Arrangement of Ventilating System (Box 3, Folder 78)
  - Old Chemistry Building - Setting for 7-1/2 H.P. Motor - S.E. Gable (Box 3, Folder 79)
  - Old Chemistry Building - Setting for 7-1/2 H.P. Motor - S.W. Gable (Box 3, Folder 80)
  - Old Chemistry Building - Details of Window Frames & Sash (Box 3, Folder 81)
  - Old Chemistry Building - Plan & Elev. of Roof (Box 3, Folder 82)
  - Old Chemistry Building - Detail of Front Gable (Box 3, Folder 83)